So in this section we are going to create an SDK.
This is for Linux and Mac platform.
So basically we just need to follow these commands to build an SDK.
SDK building is required when you want to share your changes for the iOS app with your developers in
your team, and they use this SDK as their base and they develop the apps on top of it.
Okay, so let's see how we can do that.
So this is how it can be done for Linux and Mac.
Windows is also almost the same.
I'll just show you that.
So here.
So just go to the root folder, aosp folder and then just run the environment setup once and then just
run launch SDK engine and then just make SDK.
So this will take a while.
It might take around 20 minutes or more hours depending on your PC.
So after that, you can see the output over here.
So the process is quite simple.
And so let's have a look for Windows.
So in case of Windows, the only difference is that you just make SDK and not one thing.
So in this case it could it actually builds for both Linux and Windows is located here.
So the process is quite straightforward.
So let's go ahead and do this.